http://www.kenwoodmgt.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Privacy Policy
The following sets forth the privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy” or the “Policy”) applicable to all individuals that access and otherwise use this Website of Kenwood Management Company, LLC (“Kenwood”).  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS WEBSITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THE WEBSITE. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE SHALL BE DEEMED TO BE YOUR IRREVOCABLE AGREEMENT TO ABIDE BY THE TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY SET FORTH BELOW.
Some information that identifies You as an individual ("Personal Information") is gathered when You register with this Website, or participate in community activities, focus groups and interviews, and/or other promotions (including incentive programs).  We also collect Personal Information about You to the extent that You provide it to Us online (e.g., by filling out forms on the Website or by submitting such information in an e-mail message) and offline (e.g., by filling out a comment card at one of our locations, or by registering for information concerning our activities).  You provide Your Personal Information voluntarily.
Personal Information requested may include Your name, Your street mailing address, Your email address, Your telephone number and other information, including information about Your personal or business demographics and Your home purchasing preferences.  In addition, We may ask You to enter an ID, password or similar data when You access this Website, so We can verify Your right to access certain portions of this Website. We might also obtain Personal Information about You provided to Us by Your friends/colleagues, including Your name and email address, as this Website may allow visitors to this Website to send information about the Kenwood Community to others via email.  If You choose to tell a friend/colleague about us, We may ask You for Your friend's/colleague’s name and email address. We endeavor to send to Your friend such emails. We may elect not to send the email in certain circumstances in Our discretion (e.g., if the email contains inappropriate or inaccurate information or content).  We store Your friend’s/colleague’s Personal Information for the purposes of sending these emails, tracking the success of Our referral program and promoting the Kenwood brand.  Your friend may contact Us at info@kenwoodmgt.com to request that We remove Your friend's/colleague’s Personal Information from Our database.
How do We use the Personal Information We collect:
Our goals in collecting Personal Information from You include: (i) providing You with information about Kenwood such as: press releases, pricing, properties, news and enhancements, Kenwood  events and other information We deem You may find of interest; (ii) supporting business purposes, and community planning endeavors, that We believe are reasonable and consistent with fair business practices; (iii) notifying You to provide any information regarding any property or industry information that We believe You might be interested in or that You have participated in; and (iv) contacting You concerning phased releases, available properties, upgrades, enhancements, community events or activities, services and products for new opportunities that might be of interest to You.  We also use Your Personal Information to determine other information that will be delivered to You that may be targeted to Your interests, as well as determining what periodic marketing, promotional and other notices to provide to You.  You may, at any time, choose to not receive communications from Us by "opting out" of specific mailing lists and services by sending an email requesting removal to Us at: info@kenwoodmgt.com, or by writing us at the mailing address listed below.
How We Share Personal Information:
We may disclose Your Personal Information to third parties as We deem necessary or desirable to provide products and services that You have requested.  Your Personal Information may also be disclosed to third parties on an aggregate basis and in a manner that does not reveal the personal identity of You or Your business.  For real estate professionals who are participants in our Incentive Programs, as defined below, We may disclose Your Personal Information to a third-party shipper, if applicable, so that any incentives or rewards that You have earned pursuant to the Incentive Program can be shipped and delivered to Your home or business.  We may also disclose Your Personal Information as We believe is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority. Finally, We may disclose Your Personal Information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or a portion of the Kenwood Community or upon any change in our corporate structure.
Promotions and Community Activities:
We may from time to time offer promotions, press releases, and other programs in which We may request Personal Information.  Your participation in any such promotions, activity or program will be subject to the official rules of such promotion or activity, or any release that You may sign, and any additional related conditions that may be posted on this or other applicable Web sites, or as otherwise provided.
Incentive Programs and Similar Promotions for Real Estate Professionals:
We may offer from time to time rewards programs and various other promotions and incentive programs ("Incentive Programs") specifically for real estate professionals, in which We request Personal Information, such as Your name, address, e-mail address and phone number.  The participation of real estate professionals in an Incentive Program will be subject to the terms and conditions, or official rules, of such program, any release You may sign and any additional related conditions that may be posted on this or other applicable Web sites, or as otherwise provided.
Retention and Protection of Personal Information:
Generally, We retain Your Personal Information that We collect electronically on Our server or in Our archives for as long as We reasonably need it.  We may alter this practice according to legal and business requirements. For example, We may shorten the retention period for certain Personal Information if needed to free up storage space, and We may lengthen the retention period for other Personal Information if needed to comply with privacy standards or applicable law.
We establish and maintain certain practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of electronic Personal Information stored on Our system.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, no computer system is completely secure, and while the measures We implement are intended to reduce the likelihood of security problems, there is no warranty or guarantee that Our standard security measures will prevent access to Your Personal Information.
How to modify Your Personal Information:
You may modify or update Your Personal Information by sending an e-mail to Us at info@kenwoodmgt.com.  Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within Our direct control.
Other Limits to Your Privacy and Confidentiality:
We may disclose Personal Information in special cases when We have reason to believe that disclosing the Personal Information is necessary for Us to protect or enforce Our legal rights, or when We believe that the law requires it, and for administrative and other purposes We deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services.
As more fully set forth in the Terms of Use, We operate this Website (including without limitation its registration system) and provide Our services in good faith, but on an “AS-IS”, “WHERE IS”, "WITH ALL FAULTS", “AS-AVAILABLE” basis.
Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important.  For that reason, We never collect or maintain information at Our Website from those We actually know to be under the age of 13 years.  No part of Our Website is structured to attract anyone under 13 years of age. All Website users warrant that they are not subject to the verification requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
Consent and Revisions:
By using or accessing Our services or this Website, by participating in the activities or programs outlined above, or similar activities or programs, or by providing Personal Information, You agree to this Privacy Policy.  This document supersedes any prior communication on this topic and reflects the entire and exclusive Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any revisions on this Website. Additionally, if You provide an e-mail address as part of Your registration, We may send an email to such an address to inform You of changes to this Privacy Policy.  Upon publication, the updated Privacy Policy will be deemed to replace the prior version of this Policy. We encourage You to review our Website regularly for changes. If at any time, You do not agree with the terms in the updated Privacy Policy or if You want to be removed from Our database, please let Us know using the contact information below and We will remove Your name and other Personal Information from the database.
Your Questions and Comments:
If You have questions about this Privacy Policy or would like to be removed from Our database, please send an e-mail to info@kenwoodmgt.com.
TERMS OF USE: These Terms of Use ("Terms of Use") apply exclusively to Your access to and use of this Website. This Website is presented to You by Kenwood.  These Terms of Use do not alter in any way the terms and conditions of any agreement You may have with Owner, Developer, any entity affiliated with Kenwood. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS WEBSITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THE WEBSITE. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE SHALL BE DEEMED TO BE YOUR IRREVOCABLE AGREEMENT TO ABIDE BY EACH OF THE TERMS SET FORTH BELOW.
Use of Copyrighted Materials/Trademarks:
Kenwood is the owner of this Website (“Owner”). Any materials on this Website, including without limitation any documentation, content, text, data, graphics, images, video and audio clips, interfaces or other materials, information or works of authorship (collectively the "Materials") are either owned or licensed by Owner, owned or licensed by certain property owners, owned or licensed by certain marketing independent contractors retained by Owner (“Marketing Contractors”) and may be copyrighted.  All rights are reserved. The Materials contain trademarks, service marks and trade names which are owned by Owner, and may also contain brand and product names which are trademarks, service marks or trade names of third parties which are owned by their respective owners.  Except as otherwise noted in the Website, You are hereby authorized to view, download, cache, copy and print the Materials solely for your personal, non-commercial use and not for resale or further distribution, subject to the following conditions:
(1) Any copy of the Materials or portion thereof must include all copyright notices appearing on the original; and
(2) Owner reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use by You shall be discontinued immediately upon notice from Kenwood.
Nothing contained in this Website shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any copyright, trade secret, patent, trademark or other intellectual property rights ("IP Rights") of Kenwood, Marketing Contractors or any other third-party, and, except as expressly provided herein, all such IP Rights in the Materials on the Website are expressly reserved to Owner and/or any third-party, as applicable.
Privacy Policy:
The Privacy Policy is incorporated into these Terms of Use by this reference.  By using or accessing Kenwood’s services or this Website, by participating in the activities or programs outlined in the Privacy Policy, or similar activities or programs, or by providing Personal Information, You hereby agree to the terms and conditions set forth in the Privacy Policy.
Hyperlinks to this Website:
You are granted a limited, nonexclusive right to create a "hypertext" link to this Website provided that such link is to the entry or home page of this Website and does not portray Kenwood or any of its products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise defamatory manner. This limited right may be revoked by Kenwood at any time for any reason whatsoever.  You may not use, frame, or utilize framing techniques to enclose any Kenwood trademark, logo or trade name or other proprietary information, including the Materials found at or on this Website, the content of any text or the layout/design of any page of this Website or any form contained on a page of this Website without the express written consent of Kenwood in each instance.  In addition, You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing a Kenwood name, trademark, or product name without Kenwood’s express written consent in each instance.
Links to Third-party Web Sites:
This Website may be linked to other Web sites on the World Wide Web or Internet that are not affiliated with, under the control of, or otherwise maintained by Kenwood.  If You use these links, You may leave the Website. Kenwood has not reviewed any of these third-party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites or their content. Kenwood does not endorse or make any representations about third-party sites or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them.  If You decide to access any of the third-party Web sites linked to this Website, You do so entirely at Your own risk.
Disclaimer of Warranties:
KENWOOD MAKES NO, AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL, WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED AND STATUTORY, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD-PARTY RIGHTS, COMPLIANCE WITH FEDERAL, STATE AND LOCAL REGULATIONS, THE ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, RELEVANCE, RELIABILITY OR COMPLETENESS OF THIS WEBSITE OR THE MATERIALS OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES REGARDING THIS WEBSITE, MATERIALS OR THE QUALITY, SUITABILITY, TRUTH, ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, RELEVANCE AND COMPLETENESS OF ANY CONTENT OR OTHER MATERIALS CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE. You acknowledge and agree that Kenwood operates this Website (including without limitation its registration system) in good faith, but this Website is made available to You strictly "AS IS", “WHERE IS” “AS-AVAILABLE” and "WITH ALL FAULTS".
Unlawful And Prohibited Uses:
You agree not to use this Website, including but not limited to any materials or services that You may receive through Your use of this Website:  (a) in a manner that violates any local, state, federal, foreign, or international statute, regulation, rule, order, treaty, or other law or for any purpose that is prohibited by these terms, conditions, or notices; (b) to stalk, harass or harm another person or to interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of this Website; (c) to impersonate another person or entity or otherwise misrepresent Your affiliation with a person or entity; or (d) to damage, disable, overburden, interfere or disrupt this Website or the servers or networks connected to this Website or any of Kenwood’s related websites.  You further agree not to: (i) use any data mining, robots, or similar data gathering or extraction methods in connection with this Website or (ii) attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion of the Website or any other services, accounts, computer systems, or networks connected to this Website, whether through hacking, password mining, or any other means.  You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through this Website.
Limitation of Liability:
KENWOOD, ITS PARTNERS, MARKETING CONTRACTORS OR ANY OTHER THIRD-PARTY AND THEIR AFFILIATES SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD-PARTY CLAIMING THROUGH YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE, YOUR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE, ANY CONTENT APPEARING ON THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE GENERAL CONDITIONS/TERMS OF USE, INCLUDING THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE USE OF ANY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.  IN NO EVENT WILL KENWOOD, MARKETING CONTRACTORS OR ANY OTHER THIRD-PARTY OR THEIR AFFILIATES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD-PARTY CLAIMING THROUGH YOU FOR ANY INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES ARISING FROM CLAIMS RELATED TO PERSONAL INJURY OR DEATH, LOSS OF DATA, LOST REVENUE, LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF USE OR OTHER ECONOMIC ADVANTAGE, CHANGE IN APPLICABLE GOVERNMENT REGULATIONS, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF THE ACTION AND REGARDLESS OF WHETHER KENWOOD HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.  NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS, IN NO EVENT WILL THE TOTAL, CUMULATIVE LIABILITY OF KENWOOD, ITS PARTNERS, MARKETING CONTRACTORS OR ANY OTHER THIRD-PARTY OR THEIR AFFILIATES FOR DAMAGES RELATING IN ANY WAY TO THIS WEBSITE OR YOUR USE THEREOF, INCLUDING THE GENERAL CONDITIONS/TERMS OF USE OR OTHERWISE, EXCEED FIFTY DOLLARS ($50.00). UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL WE BE LIABLE FOR EVENTS BEYOND OUR DIRECT CONTROL.
Press Releases:
The information contained within press releases issued by Kenwood should not be deemed accurate or current except as of the date the release was posted. Kenwood and their affiliates have no intention of updating, and specifically disclaim any duty to update, the information in the press releases.
Revisions to the General Conditions/Terms of Use:
You agree that Kenwood can revise the General Conditions/Terms of Use at any time without notice by updating this posting on this Website.  You agree that Your continued use of this Website after such modifications have been made constitutes Your acceptance of such revised General Conditions/Terms of Use.
General Provisions:
Enforcement of these General Conditions/Terms of Use shall be governed by the laws of the State of Maryland, excluding its conflict and choice of law principles.  The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any claims arising out of or related to these General Conditions/Terms of Use or Your use of this Website will lie in the state courts located in Montgomery County, Maryland and/or the federal courts located in Greenbelt, Maryland, and You irrevocably agree to submit to the jurisdiction of such courts.  Any legal actions against Kenwood must be commenced in Maryland within one year after the claim arose, or be barred. The failure of Kenwood to enforce any right or provision in these General Conditions/Terms of Use will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision unless acknowledged and agreed to by Kenwood in writing. In the event that a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these General Conditions/Terms of Use to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable, the remaining portions will remain in full force and effect and the offending portion shall be deemed automatically conformed to the minimum requirements of law.
Contact Us:
If you have any questions regarding the Website, please contact Kenwood by sending an e-mail to info@kenwoodmgt.com.
Pellentesque viverra dolor eu lacus imperdiet malesuada. Proin dapibus at urna malesuada placerat. Pellentesque gravida tellus at purus gravida rutrum vitae et magna. Nulla pulvinar erat lacus, ut efficitur lectus finibus id. Cras imperdiet mollis egestas. Suspendisse nisl purus, convallis volutpat arcu ultrices, interdum iaculis felis.
Maecenas imperdiet sollicitudin lectus dignissim ullamcorper. Nulla consequat auctor odio in pretium. Maecenas ac consequat sem. Nam vitae vehicula nulla, vitae blandit augue. Pellentesque sagittis sem eget posuere tincidunt. Pellentesque ut pulvinar mauris. Praesent non nunc pulvinar, bibendum est eget, molestie felis.
Sed neque nisi, ornare vulputate tincidunt vel, sollicitudin id diam. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Vivamus non urna dolor. Cras eget neque cursus, fermentum urna a, egestas erat. Sed sapien erat, sagittis nec porttitor ut, ullamcorper ut lacus. Aliquam erat volutpat. Fusce tincidunt ultrices libero, sit amet ullamcorper odio interdum sed.
"{{ cards[active].quote }}"
